Midnight Son is a drama, horror, action film directed by Scott Leberecht.
MIDNIGHT SON is the story of Jacob, a young man confined to a life of isolation, due to
a rare skin disorder that prevents him from being exposed to sunlight.
His world opens up when he meets Mary, a local bartender, and falls in love.
Tragically, Jacob’s actions become increasingly bizarre as he struggles
to cope with the effects of his worsening condition.
Forced by the disease to drink human blood for sustenance, he must control his increasingly violent tendencies
as local law enforcement narrow their focus on him as a suspect in a series of grisly murders.
Janitor, played by Tracey Walter.
Russell, played by Arlen Escarpeta.
Detective Ginslegh, played by Larry Cedar.
Bar Patron (uncredited), played by Shawn-Caulin Young.
Jacob, played by Zak Kilberg.
Mary, played by Maya Parish.
Midnight Son is a 2011 vampire horror film written and directed by Scott
Leberecht, produced by Matt Compton, and starring Zak Kilberg.
A trailer was released late October 2010.
The tone is dark and emotional.